A Guide to the William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Timberville Horse Show, two women and two men sitting on a platform, with the two men holding large wreaths of flowers. 1947, Image: P0002.03.0032; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men and one woman standing near a horse with a large wreath of flowers around its neck.1948, Image: P0002.03.0033; 2.5x3.5
  Series 7b: “Horses and Horse Events: Timberville Horse Show, 1948,” begins.
- Timberville Horse Show, a man speaking into a microphone.1948, Image: P0002.03.0034; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man sitting on a horse with a ribbon and a trophy with a number of other men and women standing nearby.1948, Image: P0002.03.0035; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men posing on their horses with a number of women and one man standing close by.1948, Image: P0002.03.0036; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man and a woman riding horses with ribbons, with four other women standing in front of them.1948, Image: P0002.03.0037; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, side view of a man riding a horse with a trophy. 1948, Image: P0002.03.0038; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, girl riding on a horse with two women standing close by.1948, Image: P0002.03.0039; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a ribbon, and another man and woman standing nearby.1948, Image: P0002.03.0040; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a ribbon and trophy, and four other individuals standing close by.1948, Image: P0002.03.0041; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man on a horse with a ribbon, and a man and woman standing in front of him.1948, Image: P0002.03.0042; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a woman on a horse and a man and woman standing next to her.1948, Image: P0002.03.0043; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a number of individuals standing next to a horse that is looking away from the camera.1948, Image: P0002.03.0044; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man riding a horse with a ribbon, and two girls standing next to him.1948, Image: P0002.03.0045; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man posing on a horse and holding a trophy.1948, Image: P0002.03.0046; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a ribbon and holding a trophy.1948, Image: P0002.03.0047; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a ribbon, with a woman and a little boy standing close by.1948, Image: P0002.03.0048; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man walking with a horse towards two women.1948, Image: P0002.03.0049; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men and two young women standing next to a horse with a ribbon.1948, Image: P0002.03.0050; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two young women standing next to a man on a horse with a ribbon.1948, Image: P0002.03.0051; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man holding a trophy and riding a horse towards two women.1948, Image: P0002.03.0052; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man holding a trophy and walking with a horse towards two women.1948, Image: P0002.03.0053; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men and a woman posing with a horse wearing a ribbon.1948, Image: P0002.03.0054; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a young man riding a horse wearing a ribbon.1948, Image: P0002.03.0055; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men and two women posing with a horse.1948, Image: P0002.03.0056; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a horse wearing a ribbon and bowing in the middle of a small group of people.1948, Image: P0002.03.0057; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a woman on a horse conversing with a woman standing on the ground.1948, Image: P0002.03.0058; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man on a horse holding his hat, with a woman standing close by.1948, Image: P0002.03.0059; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men and two women posing in front of a man on a horse with a ribbon.1948, Image: P0002.03.0060; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men and two women posing in front of a man on a horse with a ribbon.1948, Image: P0002.03.0061; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men and two women posing in front of a man on a horse, holding a trophy.1948, Image: P0002.03.0062; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two girls standing next to a man who is holding the reins of a horse.1948, Image: P0002.03.0063; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a girl and young child standing opposite a man leading a horse.1948, Image: P0002.03.0064; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a girl standing next to a man leading a horse.1948, Image: P0002.03.0065; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man leading a horse towards the camera; a number of people walking nearby or in the background. 1948, Image: P0002.03.0066; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, side view of a man riding in a horse-drawn carriage, with his horse receiving a ribbon.1948, Image: P0002.03.0067; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, man riding in a horse-drawn carriage, his horse receiving a ribbon. Two women stand in front of the horse.1948, Image: P0002.03.0068; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women standing on a platform, one holding a trophy and one holding a bridle.1948, Image: P0002.03.0069; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women standing on a platform, one holding a trophy and one holding a bridle.1948, Image: P0002.03.0070; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women standing on a platform holding a bridle and various other items.1948, Image: P0002.03.0071; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women standing on a platform holding a bridle and various other items.1948, Image: P0002.03.0072; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two young women and a young girl standing on a platform holding a bridle and various other items.1948, Image: P0002.03.0073; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women standing on a platform, one holding a trophy and another holding a horse bridle.1948, Image: P0002.03.0074; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two women standing on a platform, one holding horse bridles and the other holding ribbons.1948, Image: P0002.03.0075; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three young women standing on a platform holding horse bridles, ribbons, and a trophy.1948, Image: P0002.03.0076; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, four young women standing on a platform holding ribbons and trophies.1948, Image: P0002.03.0077; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two women and a man standing on a platform holding ribbons and trophies.1948, Image: P0002.03.0078; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three young women standing on a platform holding horse bridles, ribbons, and a trophy.1948, Image: P0002.03.0079; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women standing on a platform.1948, Image: P0002.03.0080; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women standing on a platform holding horse bridles, ribbons, and a trophy.1948, Image: P0002.03.0081; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a young woman standing on the corner of a platform holding a number of ribbons.1948, Image: P0002.03.0082; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two women standing on a platform holding ribbons and a trophy.1948, Image: P0002.03.0083; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women standing on a platform holding horse bridles, ribbons, and a trophy.1948, Image: P0002.03.0084; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women sitting in chairs on a platform holding horse bridles, ribbons and a trophy.1948, Image: P0002.03.0085; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two women and two men standing on a platform holding ribbons and trophies.1948, Image: P0002.03.0086; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men and two women sitting on chairs on a platform.1948, Image: P0002.03.0087; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man riding a horse towards the camera, with two women and a man standing nearby.1949, Image: P0002.03.0088; 2.5x3.5
  Series 7c, “Horses and Horse Events: Broadway Horse Show, 1949,” begins.
- Broadway Horse Show, a man in a suit riding a horse towards the camera, with spectators to the right.1949, Image: P0002.03.0089; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, various men on horses with spectators standing nearby.1949, Image: P0002.03.0090; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man and a woman standing in front/beside two horses.1949, Image: P0002.03.0091; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man leading a horse and holding a ribbon, with a woman standing nearby.1949, Image: P0002.03.0092; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man leading a horse and holding a ribbon, with a woman standing nearby.1949, Image: P0002.03.0093; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man leading a horse, with a woman standing close by.1949, Image: P0002.03.0094; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man and a woman standing next to a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0095; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man in a suit riding a horse and holding a ribbon.1949, Image: P0002.03.0096; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a ribbon in his hand, a woman stands next to him.1949, Image: P0002.03.0097; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man and a woman standing next to a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0098; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a woman standing next to him.1949, Image: P0002.03.0099; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a woman standing next to him.1949, Image: P0002.03.0100; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman leading a pony, which a little girl is riding.1949, Image: P0002.03.0101; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman leading a horse, which a young man is riding.1949, Image: P0002.03.0102; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman leading a pony, which a young girl is riding.1949, Image: P0002.03.0103; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman leading a pony, which a young girl is riding.1949, Image: P0002.03.0104; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman leading a pony, which a young girl is riding.1949, Image: P0002.03.0105; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman leading a pony, which a young girl is riding.1949, Image: P0002.03.0106; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman posing on a horse and holding a ribbon, with another woman standing beside her.1949, Image: P0002.03.0107; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, side view of a woman on a horse, with another woman standing close by.1949, Image: P0002.03.0108; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman leading a horse, which another woman holding a trophy is riding.1949, Image: P0002.03.0109; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman leading a horse, which another woman holding a trophy is riding.1949, Image: P0002.03.0110; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man riding on a horse with a woman standing close by.1949, Image: P0002.03.0111; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man riding on ahorse with a woman standing nearby.1949, Image: P0002.03.0112; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a young man and woman standing next to a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0113; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, two women standing next to a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0114; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, two women standing next to a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0115; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a woman standing next to him.1949, Image: P0002.03.0116; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man leading a horse with a woman standing close by.1949, Image: P0002.03.0117; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a woman standing close by.1949, Image: P0002.03.0118; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, two men posing on two separate horses, with a woman standing in front of them.1949, Image: P0002.03.0119; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man leading a horse with a woman standing nearby.1949, Image: P0002.03.0120; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man and a woman standing next to a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0121; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man and a woman standing next to a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0122; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a rider and his horse high jumping.1949, Image: P0002.03.0123; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a rider and his horse high jumping.1949, Image: P0002.03.0124; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a rider and his horse high jumping.1949, Image: P0002.03.0125; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man riding in a horse-drawn carriage, with spectators in the background.1949, Image: P0002.03.0126; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man riding in a horse-drawn carriage, with spectators in the background.1949, Image: P0002.03.0127; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man riding in a horse-drawn carriage, with spectators in the background.1949, Image: P0002.03.0128; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, view of a horse bowing underneath a rider.1949, Image: P0002.03.0129; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, rear view of a horse balancing on a small platform.1949, Image: P0002.03.0130; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, side view of a horse and rider balancing on a small platform.1949, Image: P0002.03.0131; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman riding a horse along a line of spectators.1949, Image: P0002.03.0132; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a horse rider accepting a ribbon from a woman; a man addressed the horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0133; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman attaching a ribbon to the side of a horse’s head.1949, Image: P0002.03.0134; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a horse rider talking with a woman that is about to attach a ribbon to the horses’ head.1949, Image: P0002.03.0135; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, man on a horse conversing with a woman on the ground.1949, Image: P0002.03.0136; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, man holding the reins of a horse, while a woman stands next to him holding a ribbon.1949, Image: P0002.03.0137; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man on a horse accepting an object from a woman standing on the ground.1949, Image: P0002.03.0138; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man on a horse extending a hand holding a trophy to a woman standing next to him.1949, Image: P0002.03.0139; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a close-up view of a man riding a horse, with a woman attaching a ribbon to a different horse in the background.1949, Image: P0002.03.0140; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman posing on a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0141; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a trophy in his hand, a woman standing next to him.1949, Image: P0002.03.0142; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, two women standing next to a horse with its head and neck extended forward.1949, Image: P0002.03.0143; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman posing on a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0144; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man riding a horse, approaching a man and woman standing on the ground.1949, Image: P0002.03.0145; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man on a horse holding a ribbon, with a woman standing next to him.1949, Image: P0002.03.0146; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, two men riding horses and approaching a woman holding a trophy and ribbon.1949, Image: P0002.03.0147; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, two men riding two separate horses, with a woman standing close by.1949, Image: P0002.03.0148; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man holding a trophy and leading a horse, with a woman walking next to him.1949, Image: P0002.03.0149; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, side view of a man and woman approaching a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0150; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, woman on a horse and holding a trophy, with another woman standing close by.1949, Image: P0002.03.0151; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, woman on a horse and holding a ribbon, with another woman standing nearby.1949, Image: P0002.03.0152; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man riding a horse towards a woman holding a ribbon.1949, Image: P0002.03.0153; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man posing on a horse and holding a trophy, with a woman standing beside him.1949, Image: P0002.03.0154; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman on a horse holding a trophy, with another woman standing beside her.1949, Image: P0002.03.0155; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, side view of a man and woman approaching a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0156; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, side view of a woman approaching a horse.1949, Image: P0002.03.0157; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man and woman riding on separate horses with spectators in the background.1949, Image: P0002.03.0158; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a woman riding a horse holding a ribbon and another woman standing close by.1949, Image: P0002.03.0159; 4x5
- Broadway Horse Show, a man riding a horse with a woman standing next to him.1949, Image: P0002.03.0160; 4x5
- A group of individuals riding horses at Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0161; 2.5x3.5
  Series 7d, “Horses and Horse Events: Natural Chimneys Jousting,” begins.
- A number of horse riders lined up in front of two women taking notes. One rider holds a lance. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0162; 2.5x3.5
- A line of horse riders, some holding lances, with one accepting a drink from a woman on the ground. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0163; 2.5x3.5
- A number of individuals riding horses at Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0164; 2.5x3.5
- A number of horse riders, lines up in pairs. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0165; 2.5x3.5
- A number of horse riders lining up at Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va. A few riders hold lances.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0166; 2.5x3.5
- Distant view of horse riders at Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0167; 2.5x3.5
- Distant view of horse riders at Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0168; 2.5x3.5
- Distant view of horse riders at Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0169; 2.5x3.5
- Man jousting, with spectators in the background. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0170; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of a man jousting at Natural Chimneys. Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0171; 2.5x3.5
- Man jousting, with spectators in the background. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0172; 2.5x3.5
- View of the spectators watching the jousting at Natural Chimneys. Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0173; 2.5x2.5
- Man jousting, with spectators in the background. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0174; 2.5x2.5
- Front view of a man riding a horse at Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0175; 2.5x3.5
- View of man on a horse, holding a lance. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0176; 2.5x3.5
- Four men on horseback lined up against a fence; one man holds a lance. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0177; 2.5x3.5
- A number of individuals on riding horses in a circle, many holding lances. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0178; 2.5x3.5
- A parking lot occupied by both horses and automobiles. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0179; 2.5x3.5
- A man on a horse holding a lance, with a microphone booth in the background. Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0180; 2.5x3.5
- A man and four women standing outside at Natural Chimneys, Mount Solon, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0181; 2.5x3.5
- A horse race at the Shenandoah County Fair.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0182; 4x5
  Series 7e, “Horses and Horse Events: Shenandoah County Fair,” begins. For related photographs, also see Series’ 8d and 11d.
- A woman and a young boy riding separate horses side by side, with spectators in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0183; 4x5
  Series 7f, “Horses and Horse Events: Miscellaneous,” begins.
- Men on horseback, riding in a single file line.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0184; 4x5
- Men on horseback, riding in a single file line.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0185; 4x5
- Side view of a woman on horseback, with spectators in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0186; 4x5
- Side view of a man on horseback.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0187; 4x5
- Front view of two men on horseback, with spectators in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0188; 4x5
- Various men and women on horseback at a horse show.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0189; 4x5
- Front view of a man on horseback, while another man pins a ribbon to the horse’s head.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0190; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of two men riding on horses.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0191; 2.5x3.5
- Two men and one woman riding on horseback single file.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0192; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a man riding in a horse-drawn carriage.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0193; 4x5
- Two men riding on horses.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0194; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of a man riding in a horse-drawn carriage.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0195; 4x5
- Front view of a man riding in a horse-drawn carriage.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0196; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a man riding in a horse-drawn carriage, with a man in the foreground.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0197; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a man riding a horse that is standing on its hind legs.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0198; 4x5
- Front diagonal view of a horse and rider high jumping over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0199; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a horse and rider high jumping over a fence, with spectators in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0200; 2.5x3.5
- A horse and rider high jumping a fence. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0201; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a horse and rider high jumping over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0202; 2.5x3.5
- A horse rider laying on the ground next to a galloping horse, perhaps after falling off of the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0203; 2.5x3.5
- A horse and rider completing a jump over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0204; 2.5x3.5
- A horse and rider completing a jump over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0205; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a horse and rider balancing on a small platform.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0206; 2.5x3.5
- Side/rear view of a horse and its rider standing at a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0207; 2.5x3.5
- A horse and rider high jumping over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0208; 2.5x3.5
- A horse and rider high jumping over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0209; 2.5x3.5
- A horse and rider high jumping over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0210; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a horse and its rider completing a high jump over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0211; 2.5x3.5
- A horse and its rider high jumping over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0212; 2.5x3.5
  Appears to be a double negative.
- A horse and rider high jumping over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0213; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a horse and its rider high jumping over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0214; 2.5x3.5
- A horse and its rider completing a jump over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0215; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a man on horseback tipping his hat while another man attaches a ribbon to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0216; 2.5x3.5
- A horse and its rider high jumping over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0217; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a horse and its rider completing a jump over a fence.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0218; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of a man on horseback, with his horse making a bow.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0219; 2.5x3.5
- A horse race, with spectators on either side of the track.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0220; 2.5x3.5
- A horse race, with spectators on either side of the track.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0221; 2.5x3.5
- A woman on horseback, while a man attaches a ribbon to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0222; 4x5
- A woman on horseback, while a man finishes attaching a ribbon to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0223; 4x5